what I do is show the man of ss
absolutely not for what she's mad at me
right now because I talked about her on
my podcast well a girl you self
diagnosed yourself is having autism and
I have a nephew with autism so of course
I'm going to talk but why would you
get mad you talk I can't understand
why people who talk get mad at
other people who talk like that's
what we
do but whatever I still love you Amanda
from a distance good luck that girl
she'll just and every relationship she
got for what cuz she stay in her
feelings I understand I've been I felt
attacked I get attacked sometimes and be
like what but you can't live in that but
that goes back to therapy